What's up Vikings Nation, [music] Johnny
Hecker here just signed. Just honored to
be in the purple and gold representing
you guys. Twin City stand up. Feels
amazing to finally be a Minnesota
Viking.
>> [music]
>> Long story franchise with
incredible character and [music] man
just a place that just does things
right. So I'm excited to be here with my
family. What excites me about being
[music] a part of this special teams
unit first and foremost is getting to
play you know in US Bank Stadium with
the fans [music]
and then getting to work along
with Dipo and Will. You know Will's one
of the best kickers in the league and
really excited just to get to work
[music] with him and work with Dipo and
message to the fans when third down
turns to fourth buckle up.